if you all would stop trying to kill me
in my own we could save y'all and I know
that's never gonna happen
we are able s to our core and all of the
other isms come from our ableism every
single life matters and how you all talk
about people with disabilities it's not
okay and that's all mixed up right now
with this argument I saw two people
getting on Facebook one of whom very
arrogant disease specialist basically
telling people they should die if they
don't wear masks and someone who feels
they shouldn't wear masks I think people
should wear masks it protects other
people not yourself they always bring up
the chain-link fence and golf balls like
right you can throw a golf ball through
a chain-link fence you have a bucket of
golf balls throw into the chain-link
fence some of them are gonna stay on
this side that is why we wear masks
people's lack of trust in the system
people's lack of trust and experts is
costing all of us and we can't just
mandate they trust there are people who
feel people are stupid for wearing masks
and people who feel people are stupid
for not wearing masks calling people
stupid isn't helping at all fact that we
can now make all of these accommodations
for fully able-bodied healthy people we
were not willing to make for people with
disabilities pre kovat working from home
having social interactions on zoom'
doing things that now that we all have
to do were fully able to but when it was
just for a fraction of us it's too
inconvenient
my biggest thing if we talked about any
other group like we talked about
disabled people there would be
tests in the street like there are right
now for black lives matter if we were
somehow truly able to say oh whatever
this is black people dying who cares
that is what we're saying
and we're like it only takes out the
sick in the weak it only takes out the
old free life matters even and possibly
especially if we're being selfish I know
my life matters whether or not I saved
this world my life matters but I also
know I have a piece of the key inside of
me to save humanity from itself and it's
not in spite my disabilities it is
directly because of them when this all
went down the disabled community it was
better prepared for it where we have the
resilience we have the knowledge on a
medical system we have the knowledge on
that people who are experts aren't
actually experts all of the time they're
gonna contradict each other they're
going to contradict from one week to the
next science it's not for nefarious
reasons it's because it's a new virus
and it's because experts don't agree and
the people on my side the people who
intellectually agree with me are not
doing anyone any favors by yelling at
everyone else I'm like did you convince
a single person to wear a mask on that
thread no you did not
and I don't know even if we can a big
reason people don't want to wear masks
is because they don't want to wear masks
they are uncomfortable they get people
anxiety attacks and just they do kill
they kill a fraction of the people that
would be killed without wearing them but
it's different people that are dying so
there will not be one policy that makes
everybody happy we are currently doing
with masks alone isn't working because
they're not about protecting the person
wearing them but about protecting
everybody else and so it is the healthy
and young that should be wearing them
even more than the old and people who
have immune compromised systems and yet
because people's lack of understanding
on that they feel Li shouldn't wear and
it's okay I'm okay if I get it
I knew someone who bought it and they
weren't that sick the irony is as much
as there's racism in the world as much
as there's police brutality the act of
that isn't going to turn anybody into a
disadvantage we're not going to turn
black because of what's happening all of
our societal ableism and COBIT 19
spreading through the population there
are a lot of people joining the disabled
people who will have permanent lung
damage people who are developing chronic
fatigue which often is onset with a
virus and it is highly debilitating I
have a much more mild form than most
people who have it and it's debilitating
we can still walk I can still push
myself if needed it's just I pay a
higher price then we're not pushing
myself we're going to pace
you always just listened to the experts
disabled people not the doctors and
medical teams who are telling you to
listen to the doctors didn't we tell you
to listen to the doctors we mean it
because we know they're not perfect we
know we've been told in perfect medical
advice but it goes so much deeper
because the reason people don't want to
wear masks is it's uncomfortable as it
makes them uncomfortable and so they're
gonna look for any conscious scientific
evidence to not wear one because it is
inconvenient and it is for other people
but they won't be conscious of that
they're not gonna purposely they're not
they're actually not that big of
assholes they wouldn't look at me and
say you should die your dad should die
you have a child esteem compromised they
should die they won't single out
individuals but they sure as hell will
lump us all together and say we're
expendable not worthy of accommodations
and I know no amount of debate an
argument on the scientific facts is
going to convince people they feel
differently and we live in a world where
different people feel differently they
can't understand the experience of being
disabled they can't understand the
experience of being chronically ill
until they're there until it's their
life it feels like it doesn't matter
and if what they said was true if we
were truly just a drain on society if we
only cost and didn't give I could maybe
understand it but I know deep down the
real truth is because of our resilience
because of what we have been through
because of our unique diversity and
experience everything that challenges us
everything that makes us disabled it's
the very thing that we have to give the
world and yet it's what you won't let us
give because you won't give us
accommodation all of the scientists who
could be working 20 hours a week but
they're not because you need them to
work 40 hours a week who have the actual
condition you're studying we're walking
around as data points not able to
connect our data not able to help one
another there are government's our
experts can't solve this
there's no expert who knows how to do
that we can only do it together one
expert you can bring on a doctor who
agrees you can bring on a doctor who
disagrees
if we're gonna trust expertise we need
panels of expertise and they can't be
the media can't decide who those experts
are if I could bring what was in my body
and my brain out into the world yeah I'm
doing this best I
this he's the Christ the world know
those of you that join us those of you
who are gonna be in debilitated by this
disease in the short term and those
especially we're gonna have long-term
implications for the rest of their lives
will be devastated you will go through a
deep mourning process and then you'll
join the rest of us the sages the people
who have so much to give but the world
won't trust you
the world won't look at you for
expertise but it is changing say wow
it's really suck so the people who are
on your side are turning people off of
your side because they're acting like
asshats what they think as more people
should act like asshats
and it's in the racism it's in a little
bit I've yet to hear a viable option to
get people to be less racist do the work
or the stuff so what you mean is well
they do the exact same work you did and
come to the exact same conclusion they
have their life experiences any tests
anything that could help people be less
racist would have to be able to be used
on the anti-racist themselves to hate
racist sauce I think it can't work there
can't work through it is racism
so if learning more history you think is
gonna help people be less racist when
they throw back
facts that you like there's more more
white people and slaves and there does
that make you hate them less nope facts
aren't gonna work what does work is
curiosity I can have curiosity around
people's ableism but also on days like
today like can you just stop trying to
kill me and mine so we can save you cuz
every life matters and the very ones we
seem to deem as the least worthy
actually have the most to give all of
our isms racism homophobia sexism stem
from ableism racism says you are X
because you are in this race ableism
says it matters it all of it you were X
you're stupid it shouldn't matter if
you're stupid said people's lack of
information experts caught me didn't be
like but I'm the expert you fucking
idiot has made no one change their mind
ever a history of time oh why do you
believe that tell me more
oh but what if what if you had a bucket
of golf balls and you threw them in a
chain-link fence
someone get through but wouldn't some
stay on this side that's what we're
effectively doing and even that because
they throw it what what to wear the mask
I know your value I know that every
hardship you have been through every
trauma every ISM has made you who you
are what you have to give the world
I can see beauty in humanity in the
individual everything just not kill each
other for the next couple of years we
can emerge into a beautiful beautiful
world that is designed for everyone so
everyone can give their gifts honor our
true diversity in the world that there
are amazing trans women with experiences
to share because of their unique lived
experience hand there are millionaire
authors who can't see that and they
still gave us Harry Potter there are
people who cannot understand that when
you say black lives matter you are
saying every life matters please let my
life matter but the life of my loved
ones matter and so they hear you saying
all lives don't matter
we are never all going to agree and it's
never gonna be the privileged and the
healthy uh-huh
do the work they can't they can't
understand they got their own shit going
on this video is already way too long to
pose yeah oh but just stop trying to
kill me and people like me but that's
not gonna happen
ironically we just have to save the
world I even even then you might not see
our worth but you won't need to because
my health and safety and my ability to
give my gifts won't be dependent on your
feeble ISM or lack thereof enough of us
just need to come together and create
tools there are things in the work
oxytocin 36 is coming I'll do a video on
that when I'm not in this raw state so
we can truly get humanity to fall in
love with itself and takes care of the
isms yelling at someone not to be racist
is never gonna make them not racist
we're less racist because we're all
racist sitting with people
seeing their humanity getting to know
them falling in love with the other
human being in front of you it's how we
do it all but don't want me to die they
just want people like me to die because
they see us as a burden instead of what
we truly are a gift the savior for
Humanity a better world is on its way
and we all get to participate in
creating that and we all get to have off
days take